[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
Ah!
啊!
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Ah!
啊!
[belches]
[打嗝]
How's that, Tina?
[giggles]
怎么样，蒂娜？
[咯咯笑]
No, Timmy!
不，蒂米！
We want a hiccup!
我们想要打嗝！
Try this!
试试这个！
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
[firefighter's bell ringing]
[消防员的铃声响起]
both: [hiccups]
两人：[打嗝]
- Oh!
- Whoa!
- 哦！
- 哇！
Yes!
是的！
We have created the worst
case of hiccups in history!
我们创造了最糟糕的情况
历史上的打嗝案例！
[laughs]
[笑]
This is gonna
make a great prank!
这将
搞个大恶作剧！
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
- [groans]
- Aw!
- [呻吟]
- 噢！
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
It tickles!
好痒啊！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
What was that?
那是什么？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistles]
[口哨声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[whistles]
[口哨声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
That's it.
就是这样。
[hiccupping rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
[squeals]
[尖叫声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Oh, no!
哦，不！
[hiccupping rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
SpongeBob, hurry up
海绵宝宝，快点
with that--
与那个——
order.
命令。
[hiccupping rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
Mr. Krabs!
蟹老板！
SpongeBob is up to
more nonsense again!
海绵宝宝高达
又废话了！
[gasps]
[喘气]
[growls]
[咆哮]
Huh?
啊？
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Mmm!
嗯！
[gags]
[笑点]
[Krabby Patties ricocheting]
[蟹肉饼弹跳]
[sighs]
[叹气]
Two whole days
without nonsense.
整整两天
没有废话。
T'were a good run,
Mr. Squidward.
跑得很好，
章鱼哥先生。
But we both knew
it couldn't last.
但我们都知道
它无法持续下去。
- [hiccups]
- SpongeBob!
- [打嗝]
- 海绵宝宝！
What shenanigans
are you up to now?
什么恶作剧
你现在还好吗？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
I think I'm coming--
[hiccups]
我想我会来——
[打嗝]
down with something,
Mr. Kra--[hiccups]
因某事而沮丧，
Kra先生——[打嗝]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
You've just got a case
of the hiccups, son!
您刚刚接到一个案例
打嗝了，儿子！
Are they dangerous?
它们危险吗？
Of course not!
当然不是！
I have a foolproof hiccup cure,
我有万无一失的打嗝疗法
using an old Navy trick!
使用海军的老把戏！
Old Navy trick?
老海军伎俩？
Okay, go for it.
好吧，去吧。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
Boo.
嘘。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Huh?
啊？
I'm cured!
[giggles]
我痊愈了！
[咯咯笑]
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
Ooh.
哦。
This might be a tougher case
than I thought.
这可能是一个更棘手的案子
比我想象的要多。
Why don't you go home
and sleep it off?
你为什么不回家
然后睡觉？
Oh, but I don't wanna go!
哦，但我不想去！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
Uh, sorry, boyo!
呃，对不起，男孩！
Aw, stupid hiccups!
噢，愚蠢的打嗝！
Hmm?
唔？
Hey, hey, they're gone!
嘿嘿嘿，他们走了！
[whistles]
[口哨声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Oh, hiccups.
哦，打嗝。
Hiccups are nothing
to an old Navy man like me.
打嗝不算什么
对于像我这样的老海军来说。
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Hello, Eugene!
你好，尤金！
How's my little Krabby wabby?
我的小蟹蟹怎么样了？
Ooh!
哦！
Doing fine, now that
you're here, Puffy-kins!
做得很好，现在
你来了，Puffy-kins！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
Oh my, are you all right?
天哪，你还好吗？
[groans]
[呻吟]
SpongeBob--
[hiccups]
海绵宝宝——
[打嗝]
giving me a case of--
给我一个案例——
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
hiccups.
打嗝。
Oh, Eugene.
哦，尤金。
Hiccups aren't contagious.
打嗝不会传染。
[smooches]
[亲吻]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Me hiccups, they're gone!
我打嗝，他们走了！
Oh, your kisses
are magical, Puff!
哦，你的吻
很神奇，泡芙！
Oh, you!
哦，你！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Dear me!
亲爱的我！
I have to--
[hiccups]
我必须——
[打嗝]
powder my gills!
粉我的腮！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
I've got to get rid of these
rotten hiccups before I pop!
我必须摆脱这些
在我弹出之前就打嗝了！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[gulping]
[吞咽]
[door creaks]
[门吱吱作响]
[gulping]
[吞咽]
Oh hi, Mrs. Puff.
哦嗨，普芙女士。
Oh, hello!
哦，你好！
[cries out]
[喊叫]
Oh, my pompoms!
哦，我的绒球！
Oh, Pearl, I'm so sorry!
哦，珍珠，我很抱歉！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[gasps]
[喘气]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
Oh, my hiccups!
哦，我的打嗝！
They've stopped!
他们停下来了！
Go--[hiccups]
team!
走吧——[打嗝]
团队！
Yay--
耶 -
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
team!
团队！
Ugh!
啊!
I can't cheer like this!
我不能这样欢呼！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[peaceful ukulele music]
[平静的尤克里里音乐]
[gasps]
[喘气]
Rah, rah, sis boom bah!
啊啊啊啊姐姐呸呸呸！
Go, Pearl!
走吧，珍珠！
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[hiccupping]
[打嗝]
[straw slurping]
[吸管的声音]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Huh?
啊？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
No!
不！
That hiccup ruined
my precious comic book!
那一打嗝毁了
我珍贵的漫画书！
You call them hiccups?
你称它们为打嗝？
Ha!
哈!
Back in my day,
回到我的时代，
hiccups could
turn a feller inside out!
打嗝可能
把一个家伙翻过来！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Now, that's what I call
a hiccup!
现在，这就是我所说的
打嗝！
You won't believe this, folks,
你们不会相信这一点， 各位，
but there are reports of a contagious hiccup plague
但有报道 有传染性打嗝瘟疫
spreading throughout Bikini Bottom.
遍布各处 比基尼泳裤。
[laughs]
[笑]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
The hiccup plague is real!
打嗝瘟疫是真实存在的！
Save yourselves!
救救自己！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
So, what do you think, folks?
那么，你们怎么看， 朋友们？
Is it real?
这是真的吗？
Contagious hiccups?
[scoffs]
打嗝会传染吗？
[嘲笑]
What a bunch of idiots.
真是一群白痴啊。
Huh?
啊？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[stammers]
[结巴]
[explosion and screaming]
[爆炸和尖叫]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Ow!
噢！
Watch it, you clod!
小心点，你这个笨蛋！
- Hmm...
- [hiccups rapidly]
- 嗯...
- [快速打嗝]
Uh...
呃...
Huh?
啊？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
My hiccups!
我的打嗝！
They're gone!
他们走了！
Now you have 'em!
现在你有了它们！
[laughs maniacally]
[疯狂地笑]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Oh, no!
哦，不！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[grunts and groans]
[咕哝和呻吟]
You gotta help me, Squidward!
你一定要帮助我，章鱼哥！
I've caught the hiccups!
我已经打嗝了！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Huh?
啊？
You can't catch the hiccups,
you nitwit!
你无法捕捉到打嗝，
你这个白痴！
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
[stutters]
[结巴]
What an--
[hiccups]
什么——
[打嗝]
ignoramus.
无知。
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Huh?
啊？
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[panicked stuttering]
[惊慌失措的结巴]
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
- Ugh.
- Oh.
- 呃。
- 哦。
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Squidward has the hiccups!
章鱼哥打嗝了！
Run for your lives!
为你的生命而奔跑！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[hiccups and whimpers]
[打嗝和呜咽]
Must get rid of these
必须摆脱这些
hiccu--
[hiccups]
打嗝——
[打嗝]
hi--
[hiccups]
嗨——
[打嗝]
[hiccups]--iccups.
[打嗝]——打嗝。
I'll take them, Squidward.
我会带走他们的，章鱼哥。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
- Bring it in.
- [hiccups rapidly]
- 把它带进来。
- [快速打嗝]
It's not--
[hiccups]
这不是——
[打嗝]
working.
在职的。
You have to hug me back.
你必须回抱我。
[groans]
[呻吟]
You have to mean it.
你必须是认真的。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
There you go!
就这样吧！
Come to me, little hiccups.
到我这里来吧，小嗝嗝。
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Thank you, SpongeBob!
谢谢你，海绵宝宝！
I need no thanks.
[hiccups]
我不需要感谢。
[打嗝]
It's enough to know
知道就够了
my sacrifice--[hiccups]
我的牺牲——[打嗝]
will be remembered forever.
将被永远铭记。
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
I'm free!
我自由了！
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah!
呼呼呼呼！
哦，是啊！
[feet squeaking]
[脚吱吱作响]
Good-bye, Squidward.
再见，章鱼哥。
Good-bye, Bikini Bottom.
再见，比基尼泳裤。
I'll take these hiccups
我会接受这些打嗝
where they won't
harm anyone again!
他们不会的地方
再次伤害任何人！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[melodramatic music]
[情节剧音乐]
[hiccupping]
[打嗝]
both: [giggles]
两人：[咯咯笑]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[peaceful Hawaiian music]
[平静的夏威夷音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
I've got ya, SpongeBob!
我抓到你了，海绵宝宝！
Stay away, Sandy, or you'll
catch these horrible hiccups!
走开，桑迪，否则你会
抓住这些可怕的打嗝！
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Aw, don't worry.
噢，别担心。
In my new hazmat suit,
穿着我的新防护服，
I'm safer than a bowling ball
in a pillow factory.
我比保龄球更安全
在一家枕头工厂里。
Besides, I'm here to cure you
of those darn hiccups.
另外，我来这里是为了治愈你
那些该死的打嗝。
But first, I'd best
put you in quarantine.
但首先我最好
把你隔离。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[peaceful music]
[平静的音乐]
Oh, hey, guys!
哦，嘿，伙计们！
[hiccups rapidly]
[快速打嗝]
[glass squeaks]
[玻璃吱吱声]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Hoo-wee!
呼威！
That is one
industrial strength hiccup!
那是一个
产业实力打嗝！
But don't you worry none.
We'll get it out.
但你不用担心。
我们会把它弄出来。
Step aside!
靠边站吧！
This old Navy man
will take care of it!
这位老海军
会照顾它的！
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[suspenseful classical music]
[悬疑古典音乐]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Boo.
嘘。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[screams and cries]
[尖叫声和哭声]
Try drinking water
upside down!
尝试喝水
颠倒了！
Try a cheer!
尝试一下欢呼吧！
[guttural moan]
[喉音呻吟]
Put a pickle under your tongue!
把泡菜放在舌头下面！
Try eating some Snailpo!
尝试吃一些蜗牛吧！
Um, uh, okay!
嗯嗯，好吧！
[fast ukulele music]
[快速尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Hip hip--
臀臀——
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Oh...
哦...
[groans]
[呻吟]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Blah.
废话。
[meows]
[喵喵]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[moans]
[呻吟声]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Huh?
啊？
I got nothing.
我什么也没得到。
We'll have to treat it scientifically.
我们要科学地对待它。
Mm-hmm!
嗯嗯！
With tickles!
带着痒痒的感觉！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
all: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
Hooray.
万岁。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
♪ ♪
♪♪
both: Huh?
两人：啊？
both: Uh-oh.
两人：呃哦。
[rapid hiccupping]
[快速打嗝]
[fast ukulele music]
[快速尤克里里音乐]